<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.accountwizard</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <developer id="org.kde">
    <name translate="no">KDE</name>
  </developer>
  <name>Account Wizard</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">مرشد الحساب</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Съветник създаване на акаунт</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Assistent de comptes</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Assistent de comptes</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Průvodce nastavením účtu</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Zugangsassistent</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Account Wizard</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Account Wizard</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Asistente de cuentas</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Kontu-morroia</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Opastettu tilin asetus</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Assistant de comptes</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Asistente de contas</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">אשף החשבונות</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">खाता विज़ार्ड</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Fiókvarázsló</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Assistente pro Conto</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Wisaya Akun</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Procedura guidata per la creazione di account</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">ანგარიშის მორგება</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">계정 마법사</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">Account Wizard</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Accountassistent</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Pomocnik Kont</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Мастер настройки учётных записей</name>
  <name xml:lang="sa">खाता विजार्ड</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Sprievodca účtom</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Čarovnik za račun</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kontoguide</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Hesap Sihirbazı</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Майстер облікових записів</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxAccount Wizardxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">帳號精靈</name>
  <summary>Configure accounts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">اضبط الحسابات</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Конфигуриране на акаунт</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Configuració de comptes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Configuració de comptes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Nastavit účty</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Postfächer einrichten</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Configure accounts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Agordi kontojn</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Configurar cuentas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Konfiguratu kontuak</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Tiliasetukset</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Configurer les comptes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Configurar as contas.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">הגדרת חשבונות</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hi">खाते कॉन्फ़िगर करें</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Fiókok beállítása</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Configura contos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Konfigurasi akun</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Configura account</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">ანგარიშების მორგება</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">계정 설정</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">Konfigurējiet kontus</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Accounts configureren</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Ustawienia kont</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Настройка учётных записей</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sa">खातानि विन्यस्यताम्</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Nastaviť účty</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Konfigurira račune</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Anpassa konton</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Hesapları Yapılandır</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Налаштувати облікові записи</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxConfigure accountsxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">設定帳號</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
	    Accountwizard allows to edit, create, delete accounts. Accountwizard supports IMAP/POP3/Kolab account type. Account information can be found by using ispd service.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">يسمح معالج الحساب بتحرير الحسابات وإنشائها وحذفها. يدعم معالج الحسابات نوع الحساب IMAP/POP3/Kolab. يمكن العثور على معلومات الحساب باستخدام خدمة ispd.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Accountwizard позволява редактиране, създаване, изтриване на акаунти. Accountwizard поддържа IMAP/POP3/Kolab тип акаунт. Информацията за акаунта може да бъде намерена чрез услугата ispd.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'assistent de comptes permet editar, crear i suprimir comptes. L'assistent admet tipus de compte IMAP/POP3/Kolab. La informació del compte es pot trobar fent servir el servei de l'«ispd».</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">L'assistent de comptes permet editar, crear i suprimir comptes. L'assistent admet tipus de compte IMAP/POP3/Kolab. La informació del compte es pot trobar fent servir el servei de l'«ispd».</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Mit dem Zugangsassistenten können Postfächer bearbeitet, erstellt und gelöscht werden. Der Zugangsassistent unterstützt IMAP-, POP- und Kolab-Postfächer. Die Postfachinformationen sind mit dem ispd-Dienst abrufbar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Accountwizard allows you to edit, create, delete accounts. Accountwizard supports IMAP/POP3/Kolab account type. Account information can be found by using ispd service.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Kontosorĉisto permesas redakti, krei, forigi kontojn. Kontosorĉisto subtenas kontotipojn IMAP/POP3/Kolab. Kontinformo troveblas per uzo de servo ispd.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">El asistente de cuentas le permite crear, modificar y borrar cuentas. Permite usar cuentas de tipo IMAP, POP3 y Kolab. La información sobre la cuenta se puede encontrar usando el servicio ispd.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Kontu-morroiak kontuak editatzen, sortzen, ezabatzen uzten dizu. Kontu-morroiak IMAP/POP3/Kolab kontu motak onartzen ditu. Kontuen informazioa «ispd» zerbitzua erabiliz aurki daiteke.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Opastetulla tilin asetuksella voi luoda, muokata ja poistaa tilejä. Asetus tukee IMAP-, POP3- ja Kolab-tilejä. Tilin tietoja voi etsiä ispd-palvelulla.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">L'assistant de comptes vous permet de modifier, créer, supprimer des comptes. Il prend en charge le type de compte IMAP / POP3 / Kolab. Les informations de compte peuvent être trouvées en utilisant le service « ispd ».</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">O asistente de contas permite editar, crear e eliminar contas. Permite contas de IMAP, POP3 e Kolab. A información da conta pode atoparse co servizo ispd.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">אשף החשבונות/AccountWizard מאפשר לך לערוך, ליצור או למחוק חשבונות. אשף החשבונות תומך בסוגי החשבונות IMAP/POP3/Kolab. אפשר למצוא את פרטי החשבון דרך השירות ispd.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">अकाउंटविज़ार्ड अकाउंट को संपादित करने, बनाने, हटाने की अनुमति देता है। अकाउंटविज़ार्ड IMAP/POP3/कोलैब अकाउंट प्रकार का समर्थन करता है। ispd सेवा का उपयोग करके खाता जानकारी प्राप्त की जा सकती है।</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Fiókvarázsló lehetővé teszi fiókok szerkesztését, létrehozását és törlését. A Fiókvarázsló az IMAP/POP3/Kolab fióktípusokat támogatja. A fiókinformációkat az ispd szolgáltatás használatával lehet megtalálni.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Accountwizard permitte editar, crear, deler contos. Accountwizard supporta typo de conto de IMAP/POP3/Kolab. Information de conto pote esser usate per usar le servicio ispd.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Accountwizard memungkinkan untuk mengedit, membuat, menghapus akun. Accountwizard mendukung jenis akun IMAP/POP3/Kolab. Informasi akun dapat ditemukan dengan menggunakan layanan ispd.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">La procedura guidata per la creazione di account (accountwizard) permette di modificare, creare ed eliminare account. Supporta account di tipo IMAP/POP3/Kolab. Le informazioni sull'account possono essere trovate usando il servizio ispd.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">Accountwizard საშუალება გაძლევთ, ჩაასწოროთ, შექმნათ და წაშალოთ ანგარიშები. AccountWizard-ს აქვს IMAP/POP3/Kolab ანგარიშის ტიპების მხარდაჭერა. ანგარიშის ინფორმაცია ispd სერვისის საშუალებით შეგიძლიათ, იპოვოთ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">계정 마법사를 사용하여 계정을 편집, 생성, 삭제할 수 있습니다. IMAP/POP3/Kolab 계정을 지원합니다. ispd 서비스를 통해서 계정 정보를 가져올 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">„Accountwizard“ ļauj rediģēt, veidot un dzēst kontus. „Accountwizard“ atbalsta IMAP/POP3/„Kolab“ kontus. Konta informāciju tas ļauj atrast, izmantojot „ispd“ pakalpojumu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Accountassistent biedt het bewerken, aanmaken, verwijderen van accounts. Accountassistent ondersteunt het IMAP/POP3/Kolab accounttype. Accountinformatie is te vinden door de ispd-service te gebruiken.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Pomocnik Kont umożliwia zmianę, tworzenie i usuwanie kont. Pomocnik Kont obsługuje konta IMAP/POP3/Kolab. Szczegóły o koncie można znaleźć poprzez usługę ispd.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Мастер настройки учётных записей позволяет создавать, изменять и удалять учётные записи. Программа поддерживает работу с учётными записями IMAP, POP3 и Kolab. Сведения об учётных записях можно получить с помощью службы ispd.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sa">खाताविजार्ड् खातानां सम्पादनं, निर्माणं, विलोपनं च कर्तुं शक्नोति । Accountwizard IMAP/POP3/Kolab खाताप्रकारस्य समर्थनं करोति । खातासूचना ispd सेवायाः उपयोगेन प्राप्तुं शक्यते ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Accountwizard omogoča urejanje, ustvarjanje, brisanje računov. Accountwizard podpira vrste računa IMAP/POP3/Kolab. Podatke o računu najdete s storitvijo ispd.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kontoguiden gör det möjligt att redigera, skapa och ta bort konton. Kontoguiden stöder kontotyperna IMAP/POP3/Kolab. Kontoinformation kan lokaliseras genom att använda tjänsten ispd.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Hesap Sihirbazı; hesapları düzenlemeye, oluşturmaya, silmeye izin verir. Hesap Sihirbazı, IMAP/POP3/Kolab hesap türlerini destekler. Hesap bilgileri ISPD hizmeti kullanılarak bulunabilir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">За допомогою майстра облікових записів можна редагувати, створювати і вилучати облікові записи. У майстрі передбачено підтримку типів облікових записів IMAP, POP3 та Kolab. Відомості облікових записів можна отримувати за допомогою служби ispd.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxAccountwizard allows to edit, create, delete accounts. Accountwizard supports IMAP/POP3/Kolab account type. Account information can be found by using ispd service.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">帳號精靈讓您編輯、建立或刪除帳號。它支援 IMAP、POP3、Kolab 帳號類型。帳號資訊可以利用 ispd 服務取得。</p>
  </description>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <url type="donation">https://kde.org/fr/community/donations/?app=kmail-account-wizard&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://invent.kde.org/pim/kmail-account-wizard/</url>
  <url type="homepage">https://kontact.kde.org/components/kmail/</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>accountwizard</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.accountwizard.desktop</launchable>
  <releases>
    <release version="6.3.1" date="2025-01-09"/>
    <release version="6.3.0" date="2024-12-12"/>
    <release version="6.2.3" date="2024-11-07"/>
    <release version="6.2.2" date="2024-10-10"/>
    <release version="6.2.1" date="2024-09-12"/>
    <release version="6.1.90" date="2024-08-22"/>
    <release version="6.1.1" date="2024-06-13"/>
  </releases>
</component>
